The item you're going to the auction for...
It will really help Dome, won't it?
I will definitely get what I want.
I got what I wanted.
So I'm giving you this.
You have to wear it at all times.
Do not ever take it off.
Dome, you're fired.
(God never abandons us.)
(It's just the way that He helps us)
(...is different from what we've expected.)
(He created a holy land called Eden.)
(The land is abundant and fascinating.)
(He created a man from the dust of the ground.)
(Living alone in the world gradually became painful for him.)
(Because of the loneliness.)
(So God cast a deep sleep upon him.)
(The Lord took one of his ribs and created a woman.)
(God gave her to be his life partner.)
(They were living happily in the heavenly garden.)
(God had only one rule for them.)
(They were not allowed to eat the fruit)
(from the tree of knowledge of good and evil.)
(One day, the man and the woman met Satan.)
(Satan was created by God.)
(Satan tricked them to eat the forbidden fruit.)
(God was furious.)
(He told them that they committed a deadly sin.)
(He punished them by separating them.)
(Until today, the man is still working hard and living a lonely life.)
(Until the day that he returns to ashes.)
Hey, Cripple.
Don't forget to throw away broken mannequins and quality defects.
Can't you work faster?
Arm.
Let's have a drink after you're done checking these products.
You can leave the rest to Cripple to check.
I'll see you.
(They said God won't help those who don't help themselves.)
(It's not strange, isn't it?)
(If the man starts to do something to save himself from loneliness,)
(To play the role of the Lord)
(...and create the woman that he loves by himself.)
(So he will have a companion while waiting for the Lord's return.)
(When that day arrives, I will ask this question to the Lord.)
(All this time, why did you abandon us?)
Tor Thanaphob
Gun Atthaphan
Foei Patara
Namtan Tipnaree
Saiparn Apinya
Ployphach Phatchatorn
Directed by Attaporn Theemakorn
Hello, do you want to have a new life?
A better and more valuable life.
(Believe in the Lord. He will return. The judgment day is coming.)
Are you feeling that you are left alone?
(We are hiring.)
Hello.
Yes.
What kind of flower are you looking for?
I'm looking for a job.
You want to apply for a job.
I'll go tell the shop's owner.
Wait a sec.
Thank you.
I want a bouquet to welcome a significant one back.
Can you arrange it for me?
I am applying for a job here but I'm not their staff yet.
Then think of it as a test
If I like the bouquet that you make,
I'll tell the owner to give you the job.
Do you like it?
I don't know much about flowers.
So I don't know what kind of flower I should choose
for a bouquet to welcome back a significant one.
Lily of the valley.
It means the return of happiness or rebirth.
You said you don't know about the meanings of flowers.
I guess you must have some kind of intuition.
I don't think so.
It's just a coincidence.
Is it really a coincidence?
Or do you have an intuition?
What do you mean?
Who are you?
It doesn't matter who I am.
What does matter is who you are,
what you want,
and what you can do.
Let me help you.
So it's because of that.
What are you doing?
What you are seeing is real.
I just want to make sure that
what's happening has nothing to do with you.
Only God can manifest this kind of power.
If you are not Him,
then who are you and what do you want?
Why do you have the power that my God has?
I don't know what you are talking about.
Can't you stop what is happening outside?
I won't stop.
I won't stop until you stop disrespecting my God.
Stop it.
I said stop it!
The Lord.
Do you want to see me?
Hey.
Whose flower is that?
I wholeheartedly believe in God.
But I don't think he will return in the form that we expect to see.
Now I understand why you told me to give that anklet to Khatha.
Because you wanted Khatha to use the anklet
to absorb and get rid of Dome's power.
You want Dome to stay away from the status of God as much as possible.
Now I know that the anklet is never able to get rid of Dome's power.
What I experienced today,
It was pure power.
It was a great power.
It was the power of God.
How can you be sure what you experienced is the power of God?
I created many tests for Dome.
But he's not the one.
The Lord is not like that.
Anthika.
If you met the Lord like I did, you would have no doubts.
You would believe in him indisputably.
If that's what you believe,
I will prove to you...
...that what I saw and believe...
...is real.
Do you really want to cut ties with Dome?
I told you that my world is dangerous.
I don't want to put him in danger for no good reason.
Your and Dome's worlds are the same world.
Living out there doesn't mean it's safer for him than staying with you.
The power that he has,
It will never completely disappear.
It's something that is within him.
He was born with it.
Unlike you and I,
We have the power from the curses.
Go take him back here.
More importantly,
You need to accept the feelings that you have.
You are missing Dome, aren't you?
Nonsense.
I'm sick of the tight-lipped people.
I never said I miss him.
I'll borrow this book.
I return it when I'm done reading it.
Mr. Khatha.
Do you remember the phone belonged to one of the thieves named Jib?
Do you mean the phone that was left among the stolen artifacts?
Yes, I remember.
Why?
I tracked the number of the last
outgoing call of the phone found at the crime scene.
It's the number of the owner of this antique shop.
Did you involve in the robbery?
Tell me everything and I will treat you as a witness.
That's nonsense.
Jib just told me he had cool items to sell to me.
You can be charged for a fencing crime.
How would I know that they were stolen?
Most of the items sold in my shop are shady items.
I didn't buy anything from him.
He wanted to double the price.
I wasn't stupid enough to pay him that much.
Do you know if Jib knew other antique dealers?
He gave me this card.
He said if I had interesting items, I should contact this place.
They bought all kinds of antique items and offered great prices.
This is...
I got what I wanted.
If there's anything else I need in the future,
I'll be sure to take it over from you.
Do you know it?
I saw this symbol at the auction I attended recently.
Triphob, do you remember the woman who was the High Priestess?
Yes.
I think this woman might be behind everything.
I got it.
I will dig up everything about her.
I'll tell you later.
I'm sorry
Thanks.
(On the day that I found a way to escape from the room,)
(It's like you send someone to check on me.)
(To make sure that no matter where I go,)
(I will still be in the prison that you created.)
(Maybe You just tried to scare me.)
(So I would feel that I needed to run away all the time.)
(There's no way I can find my place.)
(There's no way I can settle down and create my family.)
(I hope that You are watching me.)
(I hope You feel like a winner in the game that You created.)
(Because I don't want to keep fighting in a game that I can never win.)
I'm sorry, Anne.
I'm sorry that you have to see this.
(Dear, God.)
(I can no longer wait for Your blessing.)
(If You don't come down to save me,)
(I will have to go up to see You.)
(When we finally meet, please be kind to me.)
Anne.
Hello.
I'm Ton.
You...
Your name is...
...Anne.
Anne.
Ton.
(You finally answered my prayer.)
Anne.
(But I guess my prayer wasn't loud enough.)
(Still, I want to thank you for sending Anne into my life.)
(I promise that I will do my best to protect her.)
(Although she is not perfect,)
(I will fulfill her empty life.)
Do...
not...
do...
that...
...again
You also have a heart.
A heart?
Yes, a heart.
Where?
Since we are humans.
Every human has a heart.
(Mr. Khatha)
Could you keep the noise down?
Hello.
(Mr. Khatha, do you hear me?)
If you are listening,
You don't have to worry about me.
I'm doing fine.
(I feel lonely sometimes.)
(Because I don't get to see June, Mr. Triphob, and you.)
(What you are seeing is real)
I just want to make sure that
what's happening has nothing to do with you.
Everything is fine.
I get a good sleep.
I don't have nightmares anymore.
(I hope everyone at the museum including you is happy.)
(Please take care of your health.)
(Don't die again if you can avoid it.)
How did you come here?
Don't ask anything.
You need to come with me today.
Where are we going?
Hurry and go get changed.
June, where are we going?
Come on.
What's wrong?
(I won't let You destroy this precious gift.)
(I won't let You hurt Anne the way You hurt me.)
(Never.)
I will fix it.
Your leg will be normal.
I promise.
Dome.
Dome, hurry up.
Come on.
What are you waiting for?
Let's go. Let's play that one.
Dome, why don't you spread your arms out like this?
After finishing this, let's go home.
Aren't you having fun?
I thought anyone would be happy when coming to an amusement park.
Since the place is called an amusement park.
But I'm not anyone.
But I'm having fun.
Now I understand why humans are happy when they play rides.
Because it makes you feel alive.
The moment when the ride I played was moving up high,
I thought to myself.
"Wow, this's how life is."
You are talking as if you aren't a human.
What about you?
What have you been doing after you left the museum?
Do you have any goals in life?
I'm finding a job and living my life.
What about you, June?
Do you have any goals in life?
I just found it.
I plan to play rides another 5,000 times.
So I will know what life is.
I want to understand more about humans' fear, happiness, and suffering.
You don't need to take rides 5,000 times to learn that.
But I like it.
Take your hands off it.
I'll go to the toilet.
Wait.
Are you feeling nauseous because of the merry-go-round?
Dome.
Dome, what's wrong?
What's going on?
Let's go home.
(Dome is calling.)
Aren't you going to answer it?
Yes.
Okay.
I'll see you at your apartment in half an hour.
Yes.
Is that Shorty?
Are you going out to have dinner somewhere?
It was Dome.
He called to tell that the crystal is cracking.
He also encountered something strange.
He is with Miss June.
They are heading back to Dome's apartment.
Are you going with me?
I'll drive. You drive too slowly.
Hurry and follow me.
Do you want company?
Do you want it?
How much?
1,000 baht.
300 baht for a room.
I have a room.
Can I see your face?
Alright.
1,500 baht for off-site work.
Are you okay with it?
Where is your room?
What are you waiting for?
Let's go.
Let me go.
Shh!
It's your turn.
(I'll do everything to make Anne feel like a normal person.)
(No one can hurt her, not even God.)
(Even if I have to point a knife at the Lord.)
Don't worry, Dome. I'll stay with you tonight.
I shouldn't have called Mr. Triphob.
I don't want to bother anyone anymore.
Do you think that we aren't worried about you?
Listen.
What happened at the amusement park is a big deal.
It means that
the crystal anklet that Khatha said can protect you from anything is...
not working anymore.
It means you are in danger.
Stop frowning.
Come on. Let's go in your room.
I...
want...
...a leg.
That...
...slim...
...leg.
I guess Khatha and Triphob are here.
I'll open the door.
Who is it?
You are...
Mr. Dome.
It's me, Triphob.
June.
June, hang in there.
Tell me what happened.
Dome.
Huh?
Dome is abducted.
Where, June?
Where?
Please take care of June.
Sure.
(I will do anything to help Anne.)
(Even though I have to hurt...)
(...Your man.)
Anne, are you sure?
I'm worried that the leg won't fit you again.
Maybe an artificial leg is more suitable for you.
I'll make a new leg for you.
What do you think?
Why are you changing your mind?
We are about to be happy.
But we are happy now.
We are together and live normal life.
We have each other.
We have a family.
I...
...want to be complete.
That.
It will complete us.
Why are doing this to me?
Let me go.
Do you know who he is, Ton?
That day.
At the museum.
Because of his power.
You were brought to life.
Don't you want to be free?
Free from God who has been bullying you.
This is your test.
His power can set you free.
It will set us free.
But his power,
It is being suppressed by the anklet.
Cut his leg off.
Release the power.
We will be free.
I'm sorry.
But I have to do it.
What you are doing is not what people with the right mind would do.
Think about it.
Don't listen to him.
Go away.
Mr. Khatha.
Long time no see.
Don't interrupt my plan.
I don't want to go back.
You are...
You are my mannequin.
I've been looking for you.
You are here.
I'm not your property.
Listen to me.
You need to go back to the museum with me.
You don't need to stay in Zone 16.
You will be free.
Isn't that what you want?
Don't listen to him.
Listen to me only.
No.
Dome.
You.
Anne.
What did you do to Anne?
What did you do to her?!
Dome.
You are stupid.
You were praying to the wind and the sky hoping that God would hear you.
Your God doesn't exist.
If He existed, He would have answered your prayer.
Even though you now realize who God is,
He will hear your prayer.
Shitty God.
(Your name is Anne.)
Anne.
(If we are humans,)
(Every human has a heart.)
(I want to be complete.)
He will never listen to a prayer
from a petty non-human creature like you.
You are just a cursed artifact that was kept in a display case.
A cursed artifact like you doesn't deserve to be alive.
Return to your original form.
Stay captive until the day that this world ends, stupid mannequin.
No.
He will return.
He will return with the greatest power on a Blood Moon night.
No one can stop him.
He will be the new God.
I will be the only one who stands by his side.
Dome.
Wake up, Dome.
Dome
Directed by Attaporn Theemakorn
Nanon Korapat
View Benyapa
Midnight Museum – The Mannequin
Khatha.
Dome.
Dome, are you back to normal?
You are not Dome.
Who are you?
Let's play game.
June, you also brought back here.
I didn't go anywhere.
Where are you?
I'm in the past.
In my past.