Bam.
Bam, wake up.
But I think someone is abusing your faith for their own gains.
A 		You should do what you should have done a long time ago, Khatha.
Then.
Why did things turn out this way?
I keep asking myself this question.
Again and again.
It’s like…
I’m sorry, Chan.
…someone places the thing that I want the most in front of me,
And fool me that this thing will last forever.
Then he takes it back.
If this is the fate destined to happen to him and me,
Then who chooses this fate for us?
[114 YEARS LATER]
What is that?
Hey!
Who is there?
Mr. Annop.
There’s someone here.
If you have nowhere else to go,
you can stay with me for the meantime.
I…
I have something I need to do.
Mr. Khatha.
No matter how long time has passed.
The dark power derived from Chan’s wrath still exists.
The curse that he put on me.
It also still exists.
Mr. Khatha.
Nop.
You think…
…if I change this land to a place for storing the cursed items.
What do you think about that?
Like a museum?
Are there that many items that you need to retrieve?
Um.
There are items that need to be gotten rid of.
There are items that need to be protected.
Mr. Khatha.
How long do you have to continue doing this?
I don’t know.
It may be 10 years,
20 years,
Or 100 years.
Until I have the chance to apologize for what I did to Chan.
I will continue to make amends for my wrongdoings.
Until the day he returns.
Chan.
I’m sorry.
Directed by Attaporn Theemakorn
[12.03 AM]
[10 HOURS AGO]
(It is reported that an unusual appearance of the moon in the sky.)
(It causes panic among people who witness it.)
(We contacted an expert about the moon.)
(He’s on the phone with us.)
(Can you explain what is happening right now?)
(As far as we know, the surface of the moon is expanding and breaking off.)
(How will this affect the earth?)
(If the surface of the moon continues to expand until it explodes,)
(Every life on earth will become extinct.)
[2.05 PM]
[3.30 PM]
[UN Advises People to Seek Shelters]
Do you want it?
You will be dead soon.
So you don’t need it.
Mom.
Let’s go. Hurry up.
Let’s go.
Hurry.
Okay.
Hey.
The world is coming to an end.
Why don’t you run away like everyone else?
That is 666 baht.
Wait.
If you don’t pay, you can’t open the can.
Why are you still working?
(After the incident is reported, some people went to places of worship.)
Why don’t you go pray for God to protect you?
No.
I don’t have a religion.
Actually, it would be better if the world comes to an end now.
Aren’t you afraid of death?
We all will die.
It’s inevitable.
You just don’t know death well enough.
Have you ever been dead before?
No.
I’m Death.
It’s on me.
I’ll take this too.
I’ll get hot water over there.
[3.42 PM]
[12.03 AM]
Chan.
Long time no see.
I’m glad that you are still alive until now.
The thing that I gave you must be really good.
Khatha.
You need to pull yourself together.
You did this before, didn’t you?
Do you know that our power is connected?
What I can do, you can do it too.
On the other hand, what you can do, I can do it too.
Chan.
Dome has nothing to do with this.
Please don’t hurt him.
Don’t.
Don’t!
Dome!
Khatha.
Mr. Khatha.
Chan.
It was all my fault.
If you want to punish someone, it should be me.
Punish me only.
I’ll do that.
Dome.
Dome, wake up.
Khatha.
Are you alright?
What about you? Are you alright?
I’m okay.
Where is this place?
The afterlife world?
No.
I saw this place before.
It was when I touched the terrestrial rock.
Something tells me that this is my home.
How long have we been here?
I don’t know.
But it’s not bad.
I get to spend time with you.
Don’t you want to go back to your world?
I think I’ve been living on earth for too long.
I’ve seen many people suffering from what I did.
To be honest, deep down…
I’m glad…
…that everything is coming to an end.
Have you ever heard the saying about the ostrich?
Don’t bury your head
- in the sand like an ostrich.
Did you hear it from June?
She always told odd things to you.
You are not running away from the problem, aren’t you?
Who are you?
I am above all things.
I determine destiny.
I am the creator, the ruler, and the destroyer.
Are you God?
My time had ended a long time ago.
What you are seeing is my last light.
Khatha.
Dome.
I have a request to ask you.
We need to stop the moon from exploding.
How can we stop the moon from exploding?
Dome.
It’s impossible.
You all experience times of testing.
You need to choose whether to protect your happiness,
or something more valuable than your own life.
I will return
to destroy everything that you ever have!
But.
You want me to kill…
You have choices.
I always give choices to everyone.
Do I have choices?
Do I really have choices?
If I really do have choices, why it has to be me?
Huh?
Do you know…
Do you know how many decades I have been dwelling on it?
It took me more than 100 years to make up my mind and destroy his remain.
How could you determine my destiny like this?
Now you want me to kill him again?
Answer me.
Why?
Why it has to be me?
Huh?
Why?
Believe me that I understand how you are feeling.
Similar things like this…
…have happened thousands of times.
All humans…
…are defeated.
But I believe that you can do it.
Because you are created to be like me.
You can do everything that I can.
You can save every human.
It’s up to you whether you will do it or not.
Mr. Khatha.
Since the day that I met you,
I had many questions about my life.
I was trying to find who I am.
I was trying to figure out the purpose of my life.
It seemed that I couldn’t find any answers.
But today,
I found an answer that I learn and is very important to me.
That answer is I want to be with you.
I want to be with June.
I want to be with Triphob.
I want to be with Bam.
I want to be in a world where we all live together.
Today,
If you choose to continue to live here,
I’ll stay here with you.
Whatever you choose,
I’ll be by your side.
If that’s what you choose, I’ll send you back.
If we succeed,
We all will be together again.
What do I need to do next?
Khatha.
Dome.
If it’s you, you may succeed in doing what I failed to do.
I will bet my last hope on your choice.
[12.20 AM]
Hey.
You don’t need to rush and eat it up.
We still have some time before the world comes to an end.
You.
Are you alright?
I took over his body.
Wait.
Where are you going?
June.
Calm down.
It’s me.
I’m Dome.
I took over this body from The One.
June, do you remember
the story that you told me?
About the ostrich.
They like to bury their head in the sand.
You knew that story.
Is this really you, Dome?
What are you doing here?
I’m looking for a skyscraper.
I need to be close to the moon as much as possible.
Do you have a plan?
No.
But we need to stop the moon.
Otherwise, everyone will be dead.
But.
The One is looking for a chance to take this body away from me through mirrors.
Alright.
I’ll protect you from The One.
Let’s go.
Think of this as a gift.
One day when I am gone,
Keep this as a reminder of me.
I promise you.
No matter what happens, I will protect you,
I will be by your side,
I will never leave you,
and I will never let you be in danger.
Antika.
A faithful follower of God.
I want to know…
honestly…
what you believe in.
What did you see that day?
I…
I thought that was God.
I thought he was communicating with me,
Telling me that he chose me to be his reviver.
Until now,
Deep down, you are still searching for the answer to what you saw that day.
Do you still believe in God, Antika?
Yes.
I still believe in God.
Why don’t you sacrifice your life for God?
You don’t have faith.
God will never choose you.
To welcome the return of the Lord from ashes,
Surrender the purest of souls.
What are you doing?
You are not my God.
Get up, Chan.
You need to learn this.
If you don’t have any fighting skills,
You will be a target of bullying.
Come on.
If I fight with you, I always lose.
Come on. Get up.
Alright.
I won’t force you to learn it.
From now on,
I will protect you.
I will take care of you.
I won’t let anyone harm you.
I promise.
I’m glad that you are still alive.
You came back to life.
I guess it’s not because of my curse, isn’t it?
I came back to life.
Because I have something I need to do.
You came to get rid of me
with that poisonous dagger, right?
I won’t make the same mistake again.
Let’s work things out together, Chan.
What I said will never change.
I will destroy everything that you have.
Or more than you have.
Why, Chan?
Can’t we work things out together?
No.
Because it already started.
If you want to stop it, you need to kill me.
Stop it, Chan.
I don’t want to fight with you.
I don’t want to hurt you.
Fight me.
Why don’t you fight against me?
If you don’t do that, you will lose everything.
You said you would protect and take care of them.
If you don’t get up and fight,
You won’t be able to do what you said.
Let’s end it here.
Why do we have to end up like this?
Because this is our destiny.
It finally ends.
Chan.
Get up, Chan.
When it comes to fighting skills, I lost to you.
Don’t act like you are breaking your promise.
I don’t want it to end this way.
I want us to live together like we used to.
Khatha.
Do you know?
I was always with you.
I’d never left you.
I had been watching you.
I saw you…
…no longer being alone.
I want you…
to live,
to have a happy life with your friends.
Khatha.
I’m setting you free.
There will no longer be an obligation,
a curse,
or a promise binding us together.
Now, you can choose your own life.
The moon tonight,
It’s not as pretty as the one we saw that night.
If we have another chance to lie down and watch the moon together,
That would be great.
Wouldn’t it?
Chan.
Do you have a plan for how to stop it?
Then what the hell are we doing here?
If we are going to get rid of these terrestrial rocks,
We need to use the terrestrial rock that we have.
Huh?
Dome.
You need to focus.
Go to the museum and bring the terrestrial rock here.
Stop!
You did it, Dome.
There are more of them.
We are not the only ones who are fighting with this.
It’s so beautiful.
Mr. Khatha.
How is Mr. Dome?
He’s fine.
You don’t need to worry about us.
You should go take care of Bam.
Yes.
I’ll see you at the museum.
I…
In exchange for Bam’s life,
I...
I’ll trade this.
Hey!
Dome and I are heading back to the museum.
Hello, Mr. Khatha.
I’m Dome.
I stole this body from The One.
I’m not used to seeing you in this body.
See you at the museum.
Let’s go.
You are still a fool, Khatha.
I thought you would be dead.
Can’t we talk nicely?
What do you want?
Where is Dome?
Calm down.
Let’s talk one thing at a time.
Did he tell you about it?
About the test that God gives to every human.
Do you know what?
Who tests God?
What do you mean?
I am like you.
I’m a story written in a book.
to tell about the beginning
and the end…
…of everything in the universe.
Have you ever heard about the Four Horsemen of the Apocalypse in the bible?
I am one of them.
I am one of the Four Horsemen.
We are sent to end every life in the world.
Plague.
War.
Famine.
and…
Death.
But I’m not from the bible known in your world.
My existence is real…
…in another world.
The four of us.
We went to different worlds.
Until one day.
Until one day,
when my God died.
My world also came to an end.
When my world came to an end,
Everything lost its balance.
Other worlds including the world that you are living in.
They will crumble down.
That’s the reason why I came here.
I came here to look for a new God.
You.
You are an important competitor in my game.
How did your God die?
I killed Him.
I had to kill Him.
Don’t look at me like that.
You don’t know how cruel He was.
The reason that you met Chan and Chan was killed.
They were His plan.
What He did was…
…taking the things that humans wanted the most.
Then put them
In front of the humans.
He would lure these humans…
…to select the things that would eventually hurt them.
Everyone says we have choices.
In fact, we have no choice.
We would have no choice,
If He was still alive.
Are you saying…
…you killed God
…because you want humans to have choices?
Bingo.
Otherwise,
we would have to walk on the path that He wrote.
We couldn’t change it.
There wouldn’t have been a second chance.
For us to amend our mistakes.
Where is Dome?
Stop looking for him.
That boy.
He is just another cursed item for you.
Because Dome interrupted the plan.
This test is a failure.
Dome is sent to a new test.
Khatha.
The road ahead of you,
It is long.
Your life.
It’s like a pawn in a big game.
This…
…could be our last game.
If you choose to continue to play,
You will meet many people who are just like you.
And I…
What are you saying? I don’t understand it.
No matter how hard we try to resist our destiny.
Even though we choose a different path.
There will be people who are hurt and killed because of it anyway.
The test will never end.
Until we find the chosen one.
Someone who can change the human fate that is predestined.
I hope that person will be you.
You will get to sit at the highest point.
Use your power…
to give everyone in the world…
the freedom…
to write their own story.
Khatha.
I put a cursed item in front of you.
But I won’t force you.
It’s up to you
whether you will pick it up.
In exchange for the freedom of everyone in the world,
you need to follow the path I laid for you.
Don’t follow the path laid by the previous God.
Don’t fall into traps.
Don’t search for Dome.
You already had a choice in mind.
Why are you the same old fool?
Am I wrong that I put my hope on you?
I will choose neither the path you laid for me,
nor the path laid by the previous God.
I will choose my own path.
I have to leave now.
I’m sorry for causing a lot of chaos.
It’s my style.
Good luck with the path that you chose.
We will meet again one day.
Mr. Khatha.
It’s time.
I’ll be right there.
Mom.
Who is the man in the photo with me?
He’s Triphob, your best friend from your childhood.
Do you remember him?
I’m here to pick up the flower that I ordered.
Here it is.
It’s lily of the valley.
It has a good meaning.
Are you waiting for the return of your special someone?
How is he doing?
The same.
There’s no sign that he will wake up.
Are you going to take on a journey to look for Dome?
I will take on a journey as well.
I plan to write a book.
I hope that in the end…
we all will get to be together again.
Tum has already left on a journey.
He wrote that he decided to give it another try.
even though
he may fail to change the result.
Let’s say you were not drunk.
I was the drunk one
I was drunk on love.
If I don’t do anything,
I will regret it for the rest of my life.
You know I like you.
If you like me too, why don’t you agree to be my boyfriend?
I’m tired of putting moves on you.
Sure.
Let’s date.
Really?
Yes.
Are you serious?
You don’t want it.
Of course.
Mr. Khatha, I believe we can change it.
Do you know I’ve been waiting for this for so long?
I know.
We don’t have to be God.
We can be just humans.
It looks like Mr. Tum has turned on the machine
and set the coordinates for you.
Here.
While you are away,
I’ll take care of the museum.
Please take care of the museum.
(During my long life,)
(I keep asking myself.)
(Why people are seduced by greed?)
(Why are they addicted to the things that will hurt them in the end?)
(Someone is willing to sacrifice everything to have these items in their possession.)
(It’s not because they don’t have a choice.)
(But these items give them hope.)
(The hope that the missing piece in their life will be fulfilled.)
(They receive a test forcing them to choose.)
(They have no clue what kind of result is waiting for them.)
(Just like me.)
(I chose to take on a journey.)
(To look for my missing piece.)
(I chose to leave on a journey.)
(Not because I’m going to play in God’s game.)
(But because someone is waiting for me.)
(Tum told me.)
(He believes in the marvel of science more than a myth about God.)
(While the bible said the earth was flat,)
(A scientist proved that the earth is round.)
(Maybe God is not always right.)
(We may be able to overcome the path that is predestined for us.)
(If we have faith.)
(We need to have faith in the path that we choose.)
(One day, we will find happiness)
(on the path that we choose for ourselves.)
I finally found you.
Mr. Khatha.
Let’s get out of here.
Directed by Attaporn Theemakorn
Ployphach Phatchatorn
Saiparn Apinya
Namtan Tipnaree
Foei Patara
Gun Atthaphan
Tor Thanaphob
Midnight Museum: The Magician’s Embodiment
The situation is under control.
The suspects are taken to the police station for questioning.
Stop.
Hey.
Do you hear me?